(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
公式ハッシュタグ #hololivefesEXPO24_DAY1
The concert will be starting soon.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Official Hashtag #hololivefesEXPO24_DAY1
The concert will be starting soon.
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援 OK です
※マスクの着用はお客様自身の任意でお願いいたします
Attention: To all visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is allowed.
*Mask wearing is at the discretion of the visitor.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is ok.
*You are free to wear a mask during the show.
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
オフィシャルグッズ
Tシャツ / フェイスタオル / ペンライト / ショルダーペンライトポーチ
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
Official Goods
T-shirt / Face Towel / Penlight / Shoulder Penlight Pouch
オフィシャルグッズ販売期間
当日販売：3月16日・17日
事後通販：3月16日〜4月30日
Official Goods Sales Period
Same-day Sales: Mar 16–17
Post-event Mail Order: Mar 16 – Apr 30
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「hololive 5th fes. おめでとうございます！全力で応援してます！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"Congratulations on hololive 5th fes! We're supporting you with everything we've got!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「みんなのキラキラな姿を楽しみにしてるよ！最高のライブにしよう！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"Looking forward to seeing everyone's sparkling figures! Let's make this the best live concert!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「hololive 5th fes. 開催おめでとう！ホロライブに出会えてよかった！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"Congrats on the 5th fes! I'm so glad I encountered hololive!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「世界中から応援してるよ！最高の思い出を一緒に作ろう！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"Supporting you from all over the world! Let's make the best memories together!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「ステージで輝く姿を目に焼き付けます！頑張って！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"I'll engrave your shining figures on stage in my mind! Good luck!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「ホロライブ最高！一生ついていきます！輝いて！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"hololive is the best! I'll follow you for life! Shine bright!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「5thフェス、全力で楽しんでね！最高の景色を見せてください！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"Enjoy the 5th fes to the fullest! Please show us the best view!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「いつも元気をもらってます！これからもずっと応援し続けます！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"You always give me strength! I'll continue to support you forever!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「ついに夢の舞台！全力で駆け抜けてね！大好き！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"Finally the dream stage! Run through it with all your might! We love you!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「hololive is the best! 最高の時間をありがとう！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"hololive is the best! Thank you for the wonderful time!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「みんなの歌声が大好きです！ステージ頑張ってね！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"I love everyone's singing voices! Good luck on stage!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「この瞬間を大切にしたい！最高のライブを！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"I want to cherish this moment! Have an amazing concert!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「全力で応援中！みんなが主役！輝いて！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"Supporting with all our might! Everyone is a protagonist! Shine!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「応援ボード企画！みんなの想いが届きますように！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"Support board project! May everyone's feelings reach you!"
Capture the Moment 寄せ書きボード
「一生の思い出にしよう！頑張れホロライブ！」
Capture the Moment Support Board
"Let's make this a lifelong memory! Go for it, hololive!"
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
バンダイ
Bandai
バンダイキャンディ、バンダイスピリッツより...
From Bandai Candy and Bandai Spirits...
EXPO会場でも展示中の商品をご紹介。
Introducing products currently on display at the EXPO venue.
ウエハースや一番くじなど、
Many products such as wafers
たくさんの商品が発売いたします。
and Ichiban Kuji will be released.
バンダイブース、BANDAI SPIRITSブースでは、会場限定グッズも無料配布中。
At the Bandai and BANDAI SPIRITS booths, venue-exclusive goods are being distributed for free.
プレバンではすぐに使えるクーポンももらえる。
You can also get coupons that can be used immediately at Premium Bandai.
バンダイ
Bandai
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Weiß Schwarz
楽しむ準備はいい？
Are you ready to have fun?
ヴァイスシュヴァルツの舞台でも、青春しよう。
Let's enjoy our youth even on the stage of Weiß Schwarz.
プレミアムブースター ホロライブプロダクション サマーコレクション 3月22日（金）発売。
Premium Booster Hololive Production Summer Collection releases on Friday, March 22.
ブシロード
Bushiroad
ホロスターズがヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウに登場。
Holostars appears in Weiß Schwarz Blau.
ようこそ、カードゲームの舞台へ。
Welcome to the stage of card games.
ヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウ スタートデッキ＆ブースターパック ホロスターズ 好評発売中。
Weiß Schwarz Blau Start Deck & Booster Pack Holostars now on sale.
ブシロード
Bushiroad
hololive SUPER EXPO 2024 開催を記念して
To commemorate the hololive SUPER EXPO 2024,
ホロライブメンバーのねんどろいどが 新衣装になって再登場！
Nendoroids of Hololive members are back in their new outfits!
新しいねんどろいどをお楽しみに！
Look forward to the new Nendoroids!
フリュープライズ
FuRyu Prize
フリューから『ホロライブ』プライズが 全国アミューズメント施設に
Hololive prizes from FuRyu are coming to amusement facilities nationwide.
2024年7月以降に続々登場！
Appearing one after another from July 2024!
今後国内のホロライブメンバー 全員展開予定。
We plan to release all domestic Hololive members in the future.
最新情報はキャラ広場ホロライブで検索
Search for the latest information on Chara-Hiroba Hololive.
フリュー
FuRyu
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
Capture the Moment
hololive 5th fes.
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To all visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights
due to the stage production.
声出し応援 OK です
Vocal cheering is permitted.
オフィシャルグッズ販売期間
Official Goods Sales Period
バンダイ、バンダイスピリッツより、
From Bandai and Bandai Spirits,
EXPO会場でも展示中の商品をご紹介！
we are introducing products currently on display at the Expo venue!
ウエハースや一番くじ...
Wafers, Ichiban Kuji...
ドンジャラNEOホロライブなど、たくさんの商品が発売いたします。
Many products, including Donjara NEO Hololive, are now on sale.
バンダイブース、BANDAI SPIRITSブースでは、会場限定グッズも無料配布中！
At the Bandai and BANDAI SPIRITS booths, limited items are being given away!
プレバンではすぐに使えるクーポンももらえるチャンス！
At Premium Bandai, you can get coupons to use immediately!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiβ Schwarz!
楽しむ準備はいい？
Are you ready to have fun?
ヴァイスシュヴァルツの舞台でも、青春しよう！
Let's experience our youth on the stage of Weiβ Schwarz too!
プレミアムブースター ホロライブプロダクション Summer Collection、3月22日(金)発売！
Premium Booster: Hololive Production Summer Collection, on sale Friday, March 22nd!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
ホロスターズが、ヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウに登場！
HOLOSTARS is arriving in Weiβ Schwarz Blau!
ようこそ、カードゲームの舞台へ！
Welcome to the stage of card games!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウ スタートデッキ＆ブースターパック「ホロスターズ」好評発売中！
Weiβ Schwarz Blau Start Deck & Booster Pack 'HOLOSTARS' are now on sale!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
hololive SUPER EXPO 2024開催を記念して、ホロライブメンバーのねんどろいどが、
To commemorate hololive SUPER EXPO 2024, hololive Nendoroids...
新衣装になって再登場！
...are returning in their new outfits!
新しいねんどろいどをお楽しみに！
Look forward to the new Nendoroids!
フリューから「ホロライブ」プライズが、全国アミューズメント施設に、
hololive prizes from FuRyu are coming to amusement facilities nationwide,
2024年7月以降に、続々登場！
appearing one after another starting from July 2024!
今後国内のホロライブメンバー全員展開予定！
All domestic hololive members are scheduled for release!
フリュー！
FuRyu!
推しの曲、めっちゃいい...
My favorite song is so good...
ね？
Right?
みるハコチャーン！
Miru Hako-chan!
みるハコなら、臨場感たっぷりで推しのコンテンツが楽しめる！
With Miru Hako, you can enjoy your favorite content with full presence!
みるハコ最高！
Miru Hako is the best!
推しとも増やそう！
Let's increase our circle of fellow fans!
みるハコ！
Miru Hako!
by JOYSOUND！
by JOYSOUND!
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
Capture the Moment!
さあ、始めよう
Now, let's begin
新しい世界へ
Towards a new world
共に行こう
Let's go together
巡る季節の中で
Within the revolving seasons
いつも君がいてくれたから
Because you were always there for me
この場所で重なる想い
Thoughts that overlap in this place
輝きは止めどなく溢れて
The radiance overflows endlessly
ずっと夢見てた景色が今
The scenery I've always dreamed of...
目の前に広がっている
...is now spreading out before my eyes
鼓動が高鳴る
My heart is racing
最高の瞬間を
The best moment...
焼き付けて
...etch it into your memory
#hololivefes EXPO24_DAY1 開演までしばらくお待ちください
#hololivefes EXPO24_DAY1 Please wait a moment until the start of the show.
スクリーンショット・SNSへの投稿はOKです。動画の無断アップロード・転載は固く禁止いたします。
Screenshots and social media posts are permitted. Unauthorized uploading or re-uploading of videos is strictly prohibited.
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Attention: Due to production reasons, please be aware of flashing lights.
声出し応援OKです ※マスクの着用はお客様の任意でお願いいたします
Cheering loudly is permitted. Masks are optional for all visitors.
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK. *You are free to wear a mask during the show.
オフィシャルグッズ Tシャツ、フェイスタオル
Official Goods: T-shirt, Face Towel
ペンライト、ショルダーペンライトポーチ
Penlight, Shoulder Penlight Pouch
オフィシャルグッズ販売期間 当日販売・事後通販
Official Goods Sales Period: Same-day Sales and Post-event Sales
Capture the Moment!
さあ、始めよう
Now, let's begin
新しい世界へ
Towards a new world
共に行こう
Let's go together
巡る季節の中で
Within the revolving seasons
いつも君がいてくれたから
Because you were always there for me
この場所で重なる想い
Thoughts that overlap in this place
輝きは止めどなく溢れて
The radiance overflows endlessly
ずっと夢見てた景色が今
The scenery I've always dreamed of...
目の前に広がっている
...is now spreading out before my eyes
鼓動が高鳴る
My heart is racing
最高の瞬間を
The best moment...
焼き付けて
...etch it into your memory
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
いよいよ開催！
Finally, it's here!
hololive 5th fes.
Capture the Moment
みんなで最高の瞬間を
Let's all capture...
キャプチャーしましょう！
...the best moment together!
全力で
With all our might,
応援しています！
we're cheering you on!
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
Capture the moment
hololive stage2
#hololivefesEXPO24_DAY1
開演までしばらくお待ちください
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
hololive stage2
#hololivefesEXPO24_DAY1
Please wait for the start of the performance.
Capture the moment
遠ざかっていく 僕らの軌跡が
The trail of our footsteps that fades away...
途切れないように歌うんだ もっと高く
I sing so it won't break, higher and higher
大きな声で
With a loud voice!
覚えてるかな？ 何かが始まるサイン
Do you remember? The sign that something was beginning
集まって気づけば 鼓動を奏でてた
Gathering together, before we knew it, we were playing a beat
見るだけじゃもう 足りないでしょう？
Just watching is no longer enough, right?
君も待ってる 世界があるよ
There's a world waiting for you too
楽しい予感に ほら飛び込んじゃえばいい
See, you should just dive into the fun anticipation
ときめきは止められないから
Because the excitement can't be stopped
走り出そう
Let's start running
溢れていくよ 光の真ん中
Overflowing in the center of the light
夢の先へ羽ばたける 勇気は君の願い
The courage to fly beyond the dream is your wish
みんなで繋いだ この奇跡が
This miracle we all connected together
途切れないように歌うんだ もっと高く
I sing so it won't break, higher and higher
大きな声で
With a loud voice!
言葉とか理屈に 惑わされて
Bewildered by words or logic
彷徨っても 戻れる場所があったんだ
Even if we wander, there was a place we could return to
想い思い道ゆく 僕らの旅
Our journey where each of us goes our own way
願い
Wish
だけが 見つめていたいんだよ
I just want to keep watching
夢の色が変わっても 変わらないメロディに
Even if the color of the dream changes, to the unchanging melody
君のために 僕らのために 歌おう
For you, for us, let's sing
今を描き 君と僕らの奇跡は 終わらないよ
Drawing the present, our miracle will never end
涙さえ きっかけに変えていこう
Let's turn even our tears into a starting point
信じてくれる 仲間と一緒に
Together with the comrades who believe in us
どこへだって 飛び出していこう
Let's fly out to anywhere
もっと 遠く 空を越えて
Further and further, beyond the sky
未来の僕らに まだ見ぬ君に
To our future selves, to you whom we haven't seen yet
伝えたいこと たくさんあるんだ
There are so many things I want to tell you
迎えたい今 当たり前なんかじゃない
The present we want to welcome is not something to be taken for granted
翼を広げて さあ
Spread your wings, now
歌おう
Let's sing
Take my hand 連れていくよ 光の真ん中
Take my hand, I'll take you to the middle of the light
夢の先へ 羽ばたける
We can flap our wings towards the end of our dreams
時は君の願い みんなで繋いだこの奇跡が
Time is your wish, this miracle we all connected together
途切れないように歌うんだ
I'll sing so that it never breaks off
もっと 高く 大きな声で
Higher and higher, with a louder voice
僕ら 扉 開けて
We open the door
どこまでも 響いていく メロディ
The melody that resonates everywhere
ゆっくり走れ 走れ 道に迷った時がチャンスだ
Run slowly, run, the time you get lost is your chance
みんな、今日は見に来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for coming to see me today!
目の前のことにがむしゃらで 間違いは数え切れなくて
Frantically focused on what's in front of me, making countless mistakes
一つのことに手一杯で 足元しか見えてなくて
Hands full with just one thing, only seeing my own feet
真っ直ぐ進むも キラキラした言葉も持たず
Neither going straight ahead, nor having any sparkling words
止まらずに行こう 誓いに押されそう
Let's go without stopping, seemingly pushed by a vow
忘れたくないよ ただ好きの気持ち 瞳の向こうの光を
I don't want to forget, just the feeling of liking, the light beyond my eyes
気にするのはやめよう
Let's stop worrying about it
ゆっくり走れ 走れ 道に迷った時がチャンスだ
Run slowly, run, the time you get lost is your chance
何もない 何もない 新しい僕が見つかるはずさ
There's nothing, there's nothing, I'm sure I'll find a new me
できないことばかり見えてくる いつも遠回り
I only see things I can't do, always taking the long way around
だけど昨日のようには 道が見えるなら大丈夫
But if the path is visible like it was yesterday, it's okay
踏み出してしまった道は なかなか戻り辛くなって
The path I've stepped onto has become hard to return from
これも一つの経験だ たった一人の人生だ
This too is an experience, it's my one and only life
分からないことは 分からないと言い出せない
I can't bring myself to say I don't know the things I don't know
臆病な僕を みんなは責めなかった
Everyone didn't blame me for being a coward
忘れたくないよ この僕の気持ち 誰かを演じてた
I don't want to forget, these feelings of mine, I was playing someone else
嘘はもうやめよう
Let's stop the lies now
ゆっくり走れ 走れ 風が吹いたら進む証明だ
Run slowly, run, it's proof that I move forward when the wind blows
何もない 何もない それよりも先は僕次第だから
There's nothing, there's nothing, because beyond that is up to me
できないことばかり見えてくる いつも遠回り
I only see things I can't do, always taking the long way around
だけど昨日のようには 道が見えるなら大丈夫
But if the path is visible like it was yesterday, it's okay
盛り上がってるー！？
Are you guys having fun!?
なんと今年でフェスも5回目となります！
Believe it or not, this is the 5th fes!
...毎回来てくれて
...for coming every time.
みんなの応援が聞こえて、とっても嬉しいです！
Hearing everyone's support makes me so happy!
私も、みんなの気持ちに応えられるように頑張るから
I'll also do my best to live up to everyone's feelings,
最後まで、最高のフェスになるように
so that it stays the best festival until the very end,
みんなも盛り上がってほしいぞー！
I want everyone to get hyped up too!
あの空の向こう 向こう 向こうの未来
Beyond that sky, beyond, beyond the future,
夢の続きを
the continuation of the dream.
ゆっくり走れ 腕で 体を使って
Run slowly, with your arms, using your body,
前に進もう
let's move forward.
ゆっくり走れ 走れ 道に迷った
Run slowly, run, when you lose your way,
時がチャンスだ
that's your chance.
何もない もない 新しい僕が
When there's nothing, nothing, a new me
見つかるはずさ
is sure to be found.
できないことばかり見えてくるくるいつも遠回り
Seeing only the things I can't do, always taking detours.
だけど昨日よりは明日が見えるから大丈夫
But since I can see tomorrow better than yesterday, I'm okay.
女神
Goddess
聖女
Saint
聡明
Wisdom
慈愛
Affection
博愛
Philanthropy
女神？聖女？聡明？慈愛？博愛？ですわ！
Goddess? Saint? Wisdom? Affection? Philanthropy? It's me!
あたしなんてったってお姫様 この現世に送るヒロイン
After all, I'm a princess. The heroine sent to this world.
一生暇もといイージーモードって思ったら勝手にどうぞ
If you think life is just leisure, or rather easy mode, then go ahead.
世間はいつも風向き次第 有象無象ばっかりで本当
The world always goes with the wind. It's truly full of nobodies.
人間不信になっちゃう！
I'm losing faith in humanity!
気づいたのこの世界に情も涙もないこと
I've realized there's no compassion or tears in this world.
あれもダメ これもダメ それもダメ どれもダメ
That's no good, this is no good, that's no good, nothing's no good.
現実は世知辛い
Reality is harsh.
全部大変ですわ！
Everything is so hard!
あたしなんてったってお姫様 この現世に送るヒロイン
After all, I'm a princess. The heroine sent to this world.
楽しいシナリオ混ぜ全部全部書き換えちゃうの
I'll mix in a fun scenario and rewrite everything.
だってだってお姫様 自分様の物語くらいは
Because, after all, I'm a princess. For my own story at least...
キラキラ楽しまなきゃですわ！ですわ！ですわ！
...I have to enjoy it sparklingly! I do! I do!
今に見てなさい 運命なんて大変修正し差し上げますわ
Just you watch. I'll majorly fix that thing called fate for you.
誰？誰？誰誰誰？ 裏で糸を引いてるのは誰？
Who? Who? Who, who, who? Who is pulling the strings from behind?
操り人形だなんて ごめんだわ！
I'm not going to be some puppet!
澄まし顔してても 黒幕はあの人かも
Even if they look calm, that person might be the mastermind.
まずはあたしが強くならなきゃ 未来は変わらない
First, I have to become strong, or the future won't change.
自分改革ですわ！
It's time for self-reform!
そうよなんてったってお姫様 あたしこそ最高演出家
That's right, after all, I'm a princess. I am the best director.
今日からの全ての主導権はこちらにあるわ
From today, I hold all the initiative.
だってだってお姫様 自分様で決めたことくらいは
Because, after all, I'm a princess. For the things I decided myself...
我がままに生きなきゃですわ！ですわ！ですわ！
...I have to live selfishly! I do! I do!
女神 聖女 聡明 慈愛 博愛 ですわ！
Goddess, Saint, Wisdom, Affection, Philanthropy! It's me!
みんな、コボ姫って言ってー！
Everyone, say Kobo-hime!
今日も自分勝手にエスコート 運命の針が踊り出す
Escorting selfishly again today. The needle of fate starts to dance.
顔をあげたその時 ほら世界が恋をする
When I lift my face, look, the world falls in love.
あたしハッピーエンドプリンセス この現世に送るヒロイン
I am the happy-ending princess. The heroine sent to this world.
すったもんだある日々も全部全部愛して見せるの
Even the days of trouble, I'll show you I can love them all.
ハッピーエンドプリンセス 自分様の物語くらいは
Happy-ending princess. For my own story at least...
キラキラ楽しまなきゃですわ！ですわ！ですわ！
...I have to enjoy it sparklingly! I do! I do!
艶っぽく生きなきゃですわ！ですわ！ですわ！
...I have to live fascinatingly! I do! I do!
今に見てなさい 運命なんて大変修正し差し上げますわ
Just you watch. I'll majorly fix that thing called fate for you.
女神
Goddess
聖女
Saint
聡明
Wisdom
慈愛
Affection
博愛
Philanthropy
ですわ！
It's me!
じゃあねー！
Bye-bye!
ハッピーギラパ！
Happy Gira-pa!
ねねちのギラギラファンミーティングへようこそ！
Welcome to Nenechi's Gira Gira Fan Meeting!
さあ、ペンライトと腕を高く上げて、思い切り楽しもうね！
Now, raise your penlights and arms high and have fun to your heart's content!
それじゃあ、いくよ！
Well then, here we go!
ハッピーを！ギラの！ギラパ！
Happy! Gira! Gira-pa!
カブクワ ギラギラ最高だね
KABUKUWA Gira gira, it's the best
カブクワ Yeah!
KABUKUWA Yeah!
カブクワ プリプリおめめ出す
KABUKUWA Showing off my cute eyes
カブクワ Yeah!
KABUKUWA Yeah!
I know 満足はめちゃめちゃまだ先
I know, satisfaction is still a long way off
ずっとメロメロ みんな集まれ
Always head over heels, everyone gather 'round
ゾロゾロ CHU CHU ギラパ
Zoro zoro CHU CHU Gira-pa
ギラギラギラパ ギラギラギラパ
Gira gira gira gira-pa, Gira gira gira gira-pa
目が覚めたなら元気に おはよ
If you've woken up, then a energetic 'good morning'
おしゃれなんてそっちのけで行こう
Let's go, putting aside things like dressing up
えへへっ
Ehehe
エベレストさえなふもる
Even Everest, sae-na-humoru
ノコギリタイランドです
It's Nokogiri Thailand
さあ、ファンミーティングが始まる
Now, the Fan Meeting begins
手をあげておいでよ
Hold up your hands and come
ギラパ！
Gira-pa!
カブクワ ギラギラ最高だね
KABUKUWA Gira gira, it's the best
カブクワ Yeah!
KABUKUWA Yeah!
カブクワ ピカピカスヤスヤの
KABUKUWA Pika pika, fast asleep
カブクワ Yeah!
KABUKUWA Yeah!
CHU 前髪めちゃめちゃ可愛い
CHU My bangs are super cute
ずっとベロベロ みんな集まれ
Always head over heels, everyone gather 'round
ゾロゾロ CHU CHU ギラパ
Zoro zoro CHU CHU Gira-pa
こんにちバナナと砂糖と焼酎たっぷり袋に加えましょう
Hello banana, sugar, and shochu, let's add plenty to the bag
両手でクワっと鷲掴みさもんでもんでもんでもんで
Grab it firmly with both hands, and kneat it, kneat it, kneat it, kneat it
コストコサイズの宝石 アンモナイトにミス・Ｕ・ジュエリー
Costco-sized gems, ammonite and Miss U Jewelry
カブクワ欲しくて乗りたくね？
Don't you want a stag/rhino beetle and want to ride it?
さっさっさっさっさっさっさっさ
Sa sa sa sa sa sa sa sa
もっと盛り上げていけ！
Get even more excited!
揺っさ揺っさ揺っさ揺っさ揺っさ揺っさ
Yussa yussa yussa yussa yussa yussa
いっぱい振りまくれ！
Shake it all you can!
バンバンバンバンバンバンバンバン
Bang bang bang bang bang bang bang bang
もっと騒げ！
Make more noise!
ヘイ！ヘイ！ヘイ！ヘイ！ヘイ！ヘイ！ヘイ！ヘイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
フー！
Fu!
すごーい！みんなのおかげで、ホロライブがこんな大きな会場でアイドルできるようになったよ！
Amazing! Thanks to everyone, Hololive is able to perform as idols in such a big venue!
自分に拍手！そしてみんなに拍手！
Applause for myself! And applause for everyone!
アピール上手は丸儲け
Being good at appealing pays off well
虹色グランプリです
It's the Rainbow Grand Prix
みんなそれぞれ愛してるけど
I love each and every one of you, but
やっぱり君が好き！
I like you the best after all!
ギラパギラパギラパギラパ
Gira-pa Gira-pa Gira-pa Gira-pa
強くて可愛いの
Strong and cute
ギラギラファンタスティックなノコギリは
The gira-gira fantastic saw
宝物だよ
Is a treasure
ギラパ！
Gira-pa!
カブクワ ギラギラ最高だね
KABUKUWA Gira gira, it's the best
カブクワ Yeah!
KABUKUWA Yeah!
カブクワ プリプリおめめ出す
KABUKUWA Showing off my cute eyes
カブクワ Yeah!
KABUKUWA Yeah!
カブクワ ギラパ！
KABUKUWA Gira-pa!
みんな、ありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
カブクワ ギラパ！
KABUKUWA Gira-pa!
まだまだ盛り上がっていこう！
Let's keep getting excited!
カブクワ CHU CHU ギラパ
KABUKUWA CHU CHU Gira-pa
ギラパ！
Gira-pa!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
兎田ぺこら Usada Pekora
Usada Pekora
桃鈴ねね Momosuzu Nene
Momosuzu Nene
あいつが来たんだよ
That guy's here!
3期生！
3rd Gen!
5期生！
5th Gen!
3期生！
3rd Gen!
5期生！
5th Gen!
ペコネネだー！
It's PekoNene!
ハイテンション　ビビビビ来てるよパワフルワールド
High tension! It's buzzing, a powerful world.
全開中　繋いで　イカすぜ究極のアイドル
Full power! Connect and be the ultimate cool idol.
ハチャメチャにハッピーな気分にエブリワン
Everyone's in a crazy happy mood.
首ったけ　驚愕　極楽新庄のアイドル
Head over heels, shocked, a blissful New Age idol.
イエーイ！
Yeeaah!
みんなー盛り上がってるぺこー？
Is everyone having fun-peko?
ぺこねね紹介、行くぺこか！
Shall we do the PekoNene introduction-peko?
オッケー！
Okay!
コンぺこコンぺこコンぺこー！
Konpeko konpeko konpeko!
ホロライブ3期生の、兎田ぺこらぺこー！
I'm Usada Pekora of Hololive's 3rd Gen-peko!
どーも！どーも！
Hello! Hello!
そして！
And!
ハーイ！ホロライブ5期生、みんなの心の、エナジードリンク！
Hi! Hololive 5th Gen, the energy drink of everyone's heart!
桃鈴ねねです、イエーイ！
I'm Momosuzu Nene, yeeaah!
ねねち、コール忘れてたでしょ？
Nene-chi, you forgot the call, didn't you?
えっ、何？
Eh, what?
忘れてた、さっきぺこらと打ち合わせして...
I forgot, we had a meeting with Pekora earlier...
あー、そうだ！みんなにさ、大事な、ペコネネだーって言ってもらおうって！
Oh, right! We were going to have everyone say the important 'It's PekoNene!'
そうだよ！そうだよ！
That's right! That's right!
ちょっと忘れてた、じゃあみんな、今のやり直しで！
I forgot for a bit, so everyone, let's do it over!
みんな、いいよね？記憶忘れてぺこね！
Everyone, that's okay, right? Forget your memories-peko!
ぺこらたちが二人、あの、挨拶し終わったらぺこらたちで「せーの」って言うぺこから...
After the two of us finish our greetings, we'll say 'Ready, set...' so...
ペコねねだー！って言ってくれましたか？
Did you just say "Peko-Nene"?!
やり直せん、やり直せん。
Let's redo it, let's redo it.
こんぺこ！こんぺこ！こんぺこー！
Kon-peko! Kon-peko! Kon-peko!
ホロライブ3期生の兎田ぺこらぺこ！
I'm Usada Pekora from hololive 3rd Gen-peko!
どーも！どーも！
Hello! Hello!
そして、ホロライブ5期生、みんなの心の...
And, from hololive 5th Gen, everyone's heart's...
...エナジードリンク、桃鈴ねねでーす！
...energy drink, Momosuzu Nene-desu!
せーの！
Ready, set...
ペコねねー！
Peko-Nene!
ありがとう！わー、すごーい！
Thank you! Whoa, amazing!
本当にすごーいぺこね、ねねち！
It's really amazing-peko, Nene-chi!
人がすごーいぺこじゃん！すごーいぺこだよ！
There are so many people-peko! It's incredible-peko!
うわー！会場がデカすぎぺこじゃないですか！
Whoa! Isn't this venue just way too big-peko?!
すごい音響きわたってるね！
The sound is echoing so well!
ヤッホー！
Yahoo!
おー、やってみて、あんたもやってみないよ。
Oh, try it! Why don't you try it too?
ぺこぺこぺこ！
Peko, peko, peko!
なになになにぺこ？
What, what, what-peko?
楽しいぺこね、こうやってコール＆レスポンスするのも！
It's fun-peko, doing call and response like this!
最高！
It's the best!
楽しいぺこですけども...
It is fun-peko, but...
ぺこらたちは、さっき「未来系アイドル」をちょっと歌って踊らせて...
Pekora and the others just performed "Miraikei Idol"...
もらったぺこですけど、皆さん、ぺこらたちアイドルになれてましたぺこかな？
...just now-peko. Everyone, did we look like idols-peko?
嬉しいぺこですね！
I'm so happy-peko!
なんと今日はね、ねねち先輩！何？何？何？
And today, Nene-chi senpai! What is it?
なんとインドネシアでもライブビューイングがあります！
There's actually a live viewing in Indonesia too!
えー！マジぺこ？見てますかー？
Whaaat! Really-peko? Are you watching?
Halo, Indonesia! Apa kabar? Halo!
ぜひね、このライブの感想をハッシュタグ...
By all means, please post your impressions of this live concert...
...#hololivefes24_EXPO_DAY1でSNSでたくさんアップしてくれると...
...with the hashtag #hololivefes24_EXPO_DAY1 on SNS!
ぺこらたち嬉しいぺこだよね！お願いします！
Pekora and the others would be so happy! Please do!
あと、ハート、ハートほしいなー。
Also, I want hearts...
これもお願いします！
Please give us those too!
あ、待てぺこちゃん先輩、あいたー！
Oh, wait, Pekora-chan senpai... Ouch!
まさかこの二人だと思ったぺこなんじゃない？
Didn't expect it would be the two of us-peko?
皆も驚いたでしょ！驚いたわー！どうぺこ？
Everyone was surprised, right? How was it-peko?
いや、僕も驚きました！ねねちも驚いたわ！
Even I was surprised-peko! Nene-chi too!
ぺこらはね、ねねちとが嬉しいなーって思いながら...
Pekora is so happy to be with Nene-chi...
このフェス楽し... 何そのダンス？
...while enjoying this fes... What's with that dance?
何何何何何ぺこ？ハレンチ！
What, what, what, what-peko? How naughty!
ぺこらだ、おケツが、おケツがすごいぺこですけど！
Pekora, that butt... your butt is amazing-peko!
いや、でも本当に...
Well, but really...
あ、あれする？さっきさ、コール＆レスポンス、先やっちゃったけどさ...
Ah, should we do that? We did the call and response earlier, but...
もう一回、もう一回あれやっとこ！
Let's do it one more time!
だってみんなの顔見て！真顔になっちゃった！本当だ！
Look at everyone's faces! They've become so serious! It's true!
何で真顔になってるの？そんな暇ないよなー！
Why are you so serious? No time for that!
そうだよねー！うおおおー！
That's right! Whoooo!
じゃあ、聞いてみようか。いい？
Well then, let me ask. Ready?
日本から来た人ー！
People who came from Japan!
じゃあ、海外から来た人ー！
Now, people who came from overseas!
わー！すごーい！多いねー！すごーい！
Wow, that's amazing! So many! Amazing!
すごーい、すごーい！ありがとう！
Amazing, amazing! Thank you!
まだまだ盛り上がれますかー！
Can we get even more hyped?!
嬉しいですが、なんと...
We're happy to hear that, but actually...
無料パートはここまで！
...the free part ends here!
是非ともね、気になった方は概要欄からチケットが買えるので...
If you're interested, you can buy tickets from the description...
あ、見てくれたら嬉しいなと思います！
...so we'd be happy if you watched it!
よろしくお願いします！お願いしまーす！
Please do! Please!
それじゃあ、最後行っちゃいますか？行っちゃいましょうか、行きましょう！
Well then, let's go with the last one. Shall we? Let's go.
せーの！Capture the Moment!
Ready, set... Capture the Moment!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended! Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
The free part has ended!
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!